(Dr Millstone:)I read your paper on Kuiper Belt
object-size distribution.
(Dr Millstone:)I really enjoyed it.
(Dr Millstone:)How did you correct
for the selection bias?
(Raj:)Well, I ran a simulation.
(Raj:)Allowed me to correct
for the observational efficiency.
-Oh. That's just fascinating.
-Thank you.
(Raj:)Would you like to hear more about it
at my hot tub?
(Raj:)So when do I start?
(Howard:)You didn't get the job?
How could you not get it?
(Raj:)You know, he's British, I'm Indian.
(Raj:)Ever since Gandhi,
they haven't liked us very much.
(Leonard:)Are you saying that he discriminated
against you? We should file a complaint.
That's okay. Complaint's been filed.
(Raj:)So that's it.